Guide to the COLLECTION NAME HERE, YYYY-YYYY IBT0084
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- General Presidents and Other Leaders, Series 5
  - Dave Beck Interview with Geofrey Harwood, King TV, ND; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - 24th Annual Labor Awards Honoring IBT General President James P. Hoffa, ND; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - "Every Inch There is a Stone" Jimmy Hoffa, ND (Box 3, Item 41)
  - "Hoffa," A Danny Devito Film, 1992; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - "Hoffa: A True Story", 1992; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - "Jimmy Hoffa: The Man Behind the Mystery", Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Ron Carey President, Teamsters union National Press Club Luncheon, September 23, 1992; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - "Hoffa Slate/Leedham Slate," IBT Teamster Candidate Forum, Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - "24th Annual Labor Awards Honoring IBT General President James P. Hoffa", N/A; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - "Carhaul Campaign Kick-Off Rally" James P. Hoffa, Detroit - March 28, 1999, Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - "Close-up -Jimmy Hoffa Interview, CBS Television, 1960", Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - "CNN Lou Dobbs Moneyline - Bret Caldwell Interview - September 4, 2001", Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Declaration for Democracy, Hoffa '06, 2006; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Fitz on McNeil Lehrer NewsHour, c. 1977; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - General President Hoffa's Presentation/ Speech of Nat. Over the Road and Local Cartage Motor Freight Agreement with Cent. States Supplements, Reel 2, January 25, 1964; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - General President James P. Hoffa Inauguration #1, Undated; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - General President James P. Hoffa Inauguration #2, Undated; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Greetings from General President James P Hoffa - Local Union 391: Shop Stewards Seminar, Undated; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Hardball with Chris Matthews, Hoffa, Mexican Trucking, August 01, 2001; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Hoffa Interview - ANWR, Inside Politics - CNN, January 30, 2002; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Locals and Joint Councils, series 6
  - Teamsters Joint Council 10 - New England, Building a Better Future, February 1998; Series 1
  - Teamsters Joint Council 10 - New England Delegates Conference, Building a Better Future, 1998; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Teamsters' Local Union #107: Story (11 Minutes), ND (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Thank You Teamsters Local Union 682, ND (Box 3, Item 38)
  - Minnesota USA "Honeywell Local 1145" Business Films - WCCO-TV, ND (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Montana Local Unions 45, 112, 448, 53, 370, 593, 101, 412, and 666, 2010; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - LU 237 Files, 2012; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Teamsters Joint Council 10- New England "Building a Better Future", 1998; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - Local 639 Lockout, Professional Broadcast Tape, March 14, 1987; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - A Guide to New Members, IBT Teamsters Local 480, October 18, 2002; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - IBT / JAB Press Conference and Event, May 12, 2003; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - IBT / JAB Press Conference and Event, May 12, 2003; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - IBT / JAB Press Conference and Event, May 12, 2003; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - IBT / JAB Press Conference and Event, May 12, 2003; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - IBT / JAB Press Conference and Event, May 12, 2003; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - IBT / JAB Press Conference and Event, May 12, 2003; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - IBT / JAB Press Conference and Event, May 12, 2003; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - IBT / JAB Press Conference and Event, May 12, 2003; Series 6 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - IBT / JAB Press Conference and Event, May 12, 2003; Series 6 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - IBT / JAB Press Conference and Event, May 12, 2003; Series 6 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - IBT / JAB Press Conference and Event, May 12, 2003; Series 6 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - IBT / JAB Press Conference and Event, May 12, 2003; Series 6 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - A Guide to New Members IBT Teamsters Local 450, October 18, 2002; Series 6 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Keegel - Mo Lean Local 299 Stewards, September 13, 2000; Series 6 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Local 251 Rally After Being Locked Out of Hasbro Toy Manufacturing Co., 1992; Series 6 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Local 554 - Hoffa Greeting for Stewards and Political Coordinators Training, Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Make a Wish Foundation and Teamsters Local 771 Presents: The Mother's Day Convoy, May 13, 1990; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - RTA Union Organizing, No date; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - RTA Union Organizing, No date; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - RTA Union Organizing, No date; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - RTA Union Organizing, No date; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Teamsters Local 115 John Morris Ousted, Local Philadelphia News Programs, November 15, 1999; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Teamsters "LU 97", August 15, 1995; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Lawmakers, Series 7
  - Zagri and Curtis Interview (10 Minutes) (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Interview RE: Piggyback Senator Mike Monroney by Sidney Zagri IBT Legislative Council, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Interview Regarding Piggyback (21 Minutes), 1961 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Rep. James Roosevelt "Wages", ND; Series 1 (Box 2, Item 26)
  - Senator Wayne Morse on Labor, ND (Box 2, Item 1)
  - Teamsters States Legislative and Political Meeting, 2010 (Box 3, Item 48)